http://www.cardhaus.com/privacy-policy

Home
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
Your Privacy CardHaus Games is committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide support to you. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
What information do we collect? How do we use it? When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.
How does CardHaus Games protect customer information? We use a Secure Server for collecting personal and credit card information. The secure server layer (SSL) encrypts (scrambles) all of the information you enter before it is transmitted over the Internet and sent to us. Furthermore, we do not store customer credit card information.
What about "cookies"? "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We do not use cookies to collect or store any information about visitors or customers.
Will CardHaus Games disclose the information it collects to outside parties? CardHaus Games does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. CardHaus Games may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.
CardHaus Games may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of CardHaus Games, our users, or others.
In Summary CardHaus Games is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at CardHaus.com as simple as possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
Your Consent By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by CardHaus Games, LLC. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
CardHaus Games also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibility of the linked site and CardHaus Games has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. CardHaus Games cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.
Questions and Feedback If you have any questions or feedback related to our Policies, please email us at sales@CardHaus.com
×
Subscribe to our newsletter
To Receive Exclusive offers and deals!
Email Address
© 2020 Cardhaus - All Rights Reserved
Take Me Back Up!
